regtool.com 2013-11-27

# Welcome to RegTOOL - Scan, Repair & Speed Up Your PC!

**PC Utilities, Inc is dedicated to protecting the privacy of its subscribers and any personal information submitted to any of our Internet-based services. The Privacy Policy provided here outlines how we manage and protect information whenever a subscriber transmits any data to RegTOOL.com Internet properties.**

**Web Information**   
When you, the customer, agree to purchase RegTOOL.com software, we may collect limited personally identifying information. This information, including your name, address, and email address is necessary to record and fulfill the minimum requirements of a transaction. If and when we use a payment processing merchant, we take pains to ensure that strict security measures are in place regarding the transaction of data with that merchant.

We do not share, sell or otherwise transmit your personally identifying information to third parties without express consent, this consent being expressed when you opt in to a program with the expressed right to opt out if you change your mind; or when we believe in good faith that such a transmission is required by law, such as in response to a subpoena or other orders distributed by a court or other governmental agency. 

We do not (knowingly) use or collect personally identifying data from a person who is a minor without first retaining parental consent concerning the use or collection of such data, except in the restricted circumstance wherein we respond to a request from the minor (any and all information pertaining to such a request being maintained in a form that is not retrievable); or to a request for the name of a parent, made for the purposes of obtaining consent for the collection of personally identifying data about a minor. If we collect personally identifying information about a minor, a parent may obtain from us any data that his/her child has provided and may request that we delete that data and/or to not obtain further data. The parent may make this request by contacting [_support@RegTOOL.com_](mailto:support@regtool.com).

**Cookies**   
A cookie is defined as any data string or string of information that is stored on your computer automatically when you access our servers. RegTOOL.com uses cookies (so defined) in order to provide our customers and our affiliates with faster service, to deter Denial of Service (DoS) attacks on our systems, to prevent fraudulent transactions and to facilitate the distribution of proper sales credit to our partners. Every cookie that RegTOOL assigns to machines that access our servers is non-unique and non-identifiable. All RegTOOL.com cookies are characterized as secure and non-invasive by these criteria: 

  * They are of a limited duration
  * They are less than 5KB in length
  * They are only visible to RegTOOL.com
  * They are devoid of any personally identifying information
  * They are not unique to a given computer

RegTOOL uses cookies to track affiliates, not customers. This tracking enables RegTOOL to properly assign proper payment to affiliates for their sales and for tracing activities directly related to their affiliated relationship with us. 

**Security**   
To safeguard personally identifying information, we store all transaction records in limited access servers, safeguarded by encrypted access. We do this to protect the privacy of our customers, our customers' personal data, and the security of the servers themselves. We retain the personally identifying information only long enough to complete a purchase, to deter fraud, to provide customer service, and/or to maintain your account with us. 

We take measures to assure the reliability of our security systems and the information that is contained within those systems. We take all reasonable precautions as to the protection of confidentiality, integrity, and security of your personally identifying information and to the prevention of that information’s loss, misuse or alteration. In the event that you give your express consent to share your personally identifying information with a third party, we will take all reasonable precautions to assure that the third party is aware of these security practices and that it will also take reasonable precautions to protect any personally identifying information transferred to it.

**How Information Is Used When Collected**   
We may use information in the following ways: 

  * To enable us to process, validate and verify purchases.
  * To registry you as a customer of RegTOOL, a process that facilitates our opening and maintaining a customer support account on your behalf.
  * To send email notifications about existing or new products and services. Emails are additionally sent to notify you of special offers and to contact you to reconfirm of verify (if needed) the accuracy of provided information.
  * To obtain your feedback to help enhance existing features or provide additional products and services.

We may disclose and use personally identifying information in special circumstances where doing so is necessary to enforce our service agreements. For instance, we may invoke this disclosure if doing so will help us protect our intellectual property rights. Hereto, we may also disclose or use your personal information when we believe in good faith that the law requires us to do so. We do not sell or distribute any personally identifying information to third parties for advertising purposes or outside the bounds outlined in this policy statement. 

**RegTOOL**

**What Information RegTOOL Collects**   
The RegTOOL Software does not collect any personally identifying information from your computer. Upon un-installation, RegTOOL does not leave any active or executable data on a customer's computer. A log is left on the hard drive. This log details the items detected and removed by RegTOOL. It is left as a courtesy to our customers and can be manually deleted or used as a future reference by support techs regardless of whether or not those techs are associated with RegTOOL.  

**Updates**   
Once installed, your copy of RegTOOL will routinely check in with our server to receive updates to its software. The only data value transmitted to the server at this time is the current version of the installed software. The updating process can be moderated and/or disabled through the settings dialog in the application. By default the updates are retrieved after a notification confirming that an update is available.

**Opting Out of Email Communications with RegTOOL**   
We may, from time to time, send our customers unsolicited information in the form of emails. These emails advertise or promote our commercial products and services. If you wish to opt out of receiving these emails, you may follow the unsubscribe link, provided in the email body or as directed at [_http://www.regtool.com/remove_email_subscription.php_](http://www.regtool.com/remove_email_subscription.php). By unsubscribing, you acknowledge that you will not receive future, unsolicited advertisements or promotions via email. However, you will continue to receive email communications that relate to transactions to which you have already agreed or to products or services which you have already purchased. If you do not wish to receive any email communications, including those pertaining to transactions or purchases, you may contact us as [_support@RegTOOL.com_](mailto:support@regtool.com). 

**Policy Modifications**   
We reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy from time to time. Any and all changes will be correspondingly posted here, so please check this page periodically. 

If you have any inquiries or concerns regarding this privacy policy, feel free to contact us at [_support@RegTOOL.com_](mailto:support@RegTOOL.com).
